{"text": "A most sensible approach to an annoying dilemma. However, I'm sure that Prof. Witt begins with an overarching principle, and not \"the overarching principal\" which Peter Shawn Taylor ascribes to him.", "id": "1aa95d9a-f2a8-47c8-b47d-dbc3762dd696", "ner": [["Peter Shawn Taylor", "PERSON"], ["Witt", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "and Lauren wants to take-away the freedom the kneelers are exercising, that vets have fought to protect. Has Lauren ever heard of the term circular?", "id": "715feb0f-fa8e-4f48-a90a-3107a58d452a", "ner": [["Lauren", "PERSON"], ["Lauren", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Another Harper legacy of muzzling scientists and the true dangers of asbestos! Of course, the former sheik and his oily Alberta cartel, thought a broken pipeline and oily swimming pool in every back yard were great for Canadians health also.", "id": "732a9cbc-670a-4123-a68a-519be1427080", "ner": [["Alberta", "GPE"], ["Canadians", "NORP"], ["Harper", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Ben Turok himself voted for the demise of the Scorpions and thereby assisting the criminals!", "id": "6584ad30-dcca-498e-b6da-0de841acac3f", "ner": [["Ben Turok", "PERSON"], ["Scorpions", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Darla, do you have that worksheet that I sent you that has June on it? I deleted june and july so I need your help. Thanks, Kim", "id": "5835e24e-7bbb-49d0-8723-63251ac96314", "ner": [["Kim", "PERSON"], ["Darla", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"Dr. Pineau is an expert in \"reinforcement learning\" whereby machines are taught to make unsupervised decisions in pursuit of set goals. She also builds robots and is developing a smart wheelchair.\" Didn't Arnold star in a series of movies about machines taking over??", "id": "c25b9563-8cc0-40dd-96c0-39412081590a", "ner": [["Arnold", "PERSON"], ["Pineau", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Get Real One Music - Download your favorite songs! : (For e-mailing list removal information see bottom of e-mail.) All your favorite music, all the time. Introducing Real One Music. [IMAGE] [IMAGE] [IMAGE] Now you can easily download and play music from top record labels and create a library of your favorite artists. Get Real One? Music Now . [IMAGE] [IMAGE] [IMAGE] Choose from over 10,000 artists: from Britney Spears to Willie Nelson and more [IMAGE] [IMAGE] Download 100 or more of your favorite songs each month without buying the whole album [IMAGE] [IMAGE] Every genre is available: pop to", "id": "1eb3ebb3-3ae3-4a8f-90ad-7a29677b9a17", "ner": [["Willie Nelson", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Britney Spears", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Willie Nelson", "PERSON"], ["Britney Spears", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Initial Funding of enovate account: Hello - In order to cross one more item off of the enovate setup list, I would like to pursue the initial capital contribution required under the LLC agreement of $100,000 from each member. Although we do not have loan facilities in place or final cash management protocol, I believe the initial funding can still take place. If anyone has any other thoughts please let me know. If not, I would like to schedule the initial funding for Friday, October 6th. I believe that Mary Lynne will prepare the necessary vouchers and journal entries. I", "id": "3b58c7fa-bc43-40f0-a240-0cee18534790", "ner": [["LLC", "ORG"], ["Mary Lynne", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Douglas, Melissa Phillips just called me and approved my account. I'll confirm pricing and send in your order by tomorrow", "id": "b84c9fe7-9357-47c0-a70e-156ab3e45e4f", "ner": [["Douglas", "PERSON"], ["Melissa Phillips", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "No, slavishly obeying the IranIan dictatorial government is our federal government's strength. If one thinks that this statement is an exaggeration, note that a number of years ago Justin's brother Peter produced a CBC-Iranian funded propaganda documentary that appeared on the CBC Natonal.", "id": "05dfe834-840a-470d-922a-32628a8f7864", "ner": [["CBC Natonal", "ORG"], ["IranIan", "GPE"], ["CBC", "ORG"], ["IranIan", "NORP"], ["Justin", "PERSON"], ["Justin", "ORG"], ["CBC", "ORG"], ["Iranian", "NORP"], ["Peter", "PERSON"], ["Iranian", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Opps, I goofed. The person speaking at the press conference for Trump was Steve Miller, not Smith.", "id": "8707c2ab-f51a-4b83-9700-d0db0f47d843", "ner": [["Smith", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Steve Miller", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Perfect- that's exactly right. He should read a little more Peter Schiff, a little less Marx.", "id": "00f62de9-8e62-4592-bdba-58c8e804b44d", "ner": [["Peter Schiff", "PERSON"], ["Marx", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "PEP Manager's Notebook: sounds great! I've asked Annette to set something up. MHC", "id": "67a52dc9-b049-4d09-bdcf-b1dfb59f81ab", "ner": [["MHC", "ORG"], ["PEP", "ORG"], ["Annette", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "SO2 Documentation: Hey Mike Attached is the documentation we discussed yesterday. Let me know if you have any questions/suggestions or anything. Wade", "id": "194da040-a059-47d2-bf1a-cef0cbf91567", "ner": [["Mike Attached", "PERSON"], ["Mike", "PERSON"], ["Wade", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "This editorial comin' from the censorship loving paper that repeatedly endorsed a Canadian Prime Minister who founded a white supremacist group (\"The Northern Foundation\") which called for Crystal Parker imprisonment. Andrew Alvarez really cares what you think anything, G&M. Keep on trolling though.", "id": "1cc57597-a905-4c4a-945b-7acd329739f9", "ner": [["The Northern Foundation", "ORG"], ["The Northern Foundation", "NORP"], ["Crystal Parker", "PERSON"], ["Canadian", "NORP"], ["supremacist", "NORP"], ["Prime Minister", "PERSON"], ["Andrew Alvarez", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Abraham Lincoln DID NOT own slaves. Washington emancipated his slaves in his will. There is a major difference between owning slaves in a time when it was considered normal and fighting to retain slavery when the majority of society has condemned it.", "id": "a08042ea-5277-45e2-b4b2-1725287cd8eb", "ner": [["Washington", "GPE"], ["Abraham Lincoln", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "And the dad of Omar Mateen's the Orlando shooter (an actual terrorist) supports Hillary...so what's your point?", "id": "c8015b78-9657-4291-953f-96ee003bbbeb", "ner": [["Omar Mateen", "PERSON"], ["Omar Mateen's", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Hillary", "PERSON"], ["Orlando", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "At first, I had separation anxiety. I missed all the chaos and intrigue, the lies and cover-ups and sweet talk and reconciliations and razzmatazz. I stalked my ex. I couldn't help myself. I drove up to Chappaqua and stood around for hours in the cold and slush of Bill's driveway. I bought a box of Pepperidge Farm Double Chocolate Chunk cookies at his favorite deli, hoping the aroma would lure him out of the house. Bill still had trouble written all over him. I still wanted to cover a guy who had trouble written all over him. I wasn't ready", "id": "602c6297-616f-465f-84c8-a1e5365a7041", "ner": [["Bill", "PERSON"], ["Bill", "PERSON"], ["Pepperidge Farm Double Chocolate Chunk", "ORG"], ["Chappaqua", "ORG"], ["Chappaqua", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "carried by two >San Diego Democrats, Sen. >Dede Alpert and >Assemblywoman Susan Davis >", "id": "11ac25b4-aa3b-4d65-b7e5-53a0fa6ae793", "ner": [["San Diego", "GPE"], ["Democrats", "NORP"], ["Susan Davis", "PERSON"], ["Dede Alpert", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Donny is NOT a civilian - he is their CIC. Regardless of what you think, the fact is he didn't know why it was being played. And by assuming it was 'just for him' shows that he truly does not respect the flag.", "id": "c7bbfb47-7f6b-4e36-86f8-6e1e6612c649", "ner": [["CIC", "ORG"], ["Donny", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "EXCO Resources, Inc.: Fred wanted to get this draft out today, so I had to get it back from Mary and get Robert Bruce to review it, then sent it out", "id": "c0bc8820-2826-4e6c-92f8-094d797c0f13", "ner": [["EXCO Resources, Inc.", "ORG"], ["EXCO Resources, Inc", "ORG"], ["Robert Bruce", "PERSON"], ["Mary", "PERSON"], ["Fred", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "guess Martin missed Matthews (MSNBC) comment that the impeachment train left the station during the Comey investigation - shame he cant help himself - he seems addicted to misrepresentation and fake news -", "id": "7b0229c7-d10f-4320-96a8-a56d08f0742b", "ner": [["MSNBC", "ORG"], ["Comey", "PERSON"], ["Martin", "PERSON"], ["Matthews", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Katie is a disgrace to CA and the US Senate. I blame my fellow CA voters for putting her in office.", "id": "b571e300-5a42-42cd-a493-79e4b36f15c3", "ner": [["Katie", "PERSON"], ["US Senate", "NORP"], ["US Senate", "ORG"], ["the US", "ORG"], ["CA", "GPE"], ["CA", "GPE"], ["US", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Hey, just change the state name of Hawaii to Carrie Palmer DVM.....our new 50th state!", "id": "68d7daed-26b0-4e51-8b50-48c0bff66514", "ner": [["Hawaii", "GPE"], ["Carrie Palmer DVM", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I regret to say that our Holiday Party is cancelled this year.: Ann - We'd love to help! Just let us know what the family needs... .. Kim & John", "id": "de82ac10-fd9a-4b85-83bf-0eb680841a4a", "ner": [["Ann", "PERSON"], ["Kim", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"], ["Holiday Party", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "I think we may take it as a given that whatever the results of the NAFTA negotiations, Trump will describe it as the \"Best Deal Ever For Americans!\" even if the whole thing collapses. And his base will buy it, hook, line and sinker.", "id": "24bfd8d8-8d0a-4799-b51e-636fe4f661e8", "ner": [["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["NAFTA", "ORG"], ["Americans", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "\"Mark Helfrich’s teams had winning streaks of six, eight and nine games during his first three seasons as Oregon’s head football coach.\" Make that \"Chip Kelley's team had winning streaks of six, eight and nine games during the first three seasons with Mark Helfrich as head coach...\"", "id": "555788e7-3cbc-493d-b0e0-be8baca5e19e", "ner": [["Mark Helfrich", "PERSON"], ["Mark Helfrich’s", "PERSON"], ["Oregon", "GPE"], ["Chip Kelley", "PERSON"], ["Mark Helfrich", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Mr. Terrance has done little to reassure investors of his independence. The proof, of course, will come in the performance. Fortunately, the mess at Enron gives the S.E.C. a golden opportunity to counter the puppy image. It will take time for the commission to determine if the company's accounting was proper. But there need be no delay in forcing Enron to clearly explain", "id": "7a305e16-d918-4b0e-83f4-1bea3aaf33b1", "ner": [["S.E.C", "ORG"], ["S.E.C.", "ORG"], ["Enron", "ORG"], ["Terrance", "PERSON"], ["Mr. Terrance", "PERSON"], ["Enron", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "NAES meeting in Barton Creek in Austin: [Kevin Zimmerman 412 355 8650", "id": "9702e1ae-f9a2-44e3-b7aa-b3df388529d3", "ner": [["NAES", "ORG"], ["Austin", "GPE"], ["412 355 8650", "USER_ID"], ["Barton Creek", "GPE"], ["Kevin Zimmerman", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Robin Treadwell's Call: Robin, Diomedes was not eligible for severance because of outstanding expense reports", "id": "6e35072f-53ce-4b37-81f1-9173f70857c6", "ner": [["Robin Treadwell's", "PERSON"], ["Robin", "PERSON"], ["Diomedes", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "set hard rules, order refunds if justified and just handle it. The state Capitol wouldn't be so overheated and there'd be less pressure on the generators if the Feds did their job. ?? In that regard, Californians now are beginning to discover another group: Bush and the Blackouts. ?? The boos are becoming more raucous. LOAD-DATE: May 10, 2001 ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ? 22 of 110 DOCUMENTS ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? ?? Copyright 2001 / Los Angeles Times ?? ?? ?? ?? ??", "id": "f2e8967a-8b2a-4064-8728-c88741fa7ca6", "ner": [["Los Angeles Times", "ORG"], ["Californians", "NORP"], ["Bush", "PERSON"], ["Capitol", "ORG"], ["Bush", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "So the Laura fan who shot up the Republican baseball practice was just fake news then?", "id": "7414ca53-b0f3-49b9-bcd7-d65930ebf4c0", "ner": [["Republican", "NORP"], ["Laura", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Tell'em. Its absurd how stuck on that overblown incident people are, but let's forget every gaffe that Hillary has ever dropped... because Trump is unacceptable. Gary/Bill all the way in 2016.", "id": "d8c6dc35-be72-4651-b0b3-00608b9221bf", "ner": [["Hillary", "PERSON"], ["Gary", "PERSON"], ["Gary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Bill", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Bill", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "The story broke less than two weeks ago. Trudeau was in Ireland at the time and did, indeed, hope that the story would be dead before he returned home.", "id": "86119416-6f49-4d21-aef8-4a44cb4399d4", "ner": [["Ireland", "GPE"], ["Trudeau", "PERSON"], ["Trudeau", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "The words you're quoting are from Trump's spokesperson Sean Spicer, and it's quite clearly spin. So it's not \"according to this story\", it's according to Trump's hired Spin Doctor. Not sure if you're intentionally being dishonest or not, but context is important.", "id": "afc08930-510e-478b-829a-7fb759f3d105", "ner": [["Sean Spicer", "PERSON"], ["Trump's", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump's", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "ORG"], ["Trump", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "VY Notice: Woody, I think I've received email from Joanna Beckerman but I can't find an email address for her. Would you send her address to me please", "id": "922a8410-6b87-497a-b418-f1473bb6244a", "ner": [["Joanna Beckerman", "PERSON"], ["Woody", "PERSON"], ["VY", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Was it an actual joke or urban legend when Bush said \"Miss me yet?\" a few months into Trumps term?", "id": "aca86355-1b52-49c5-b4b2-c370fb24e829", "ner": [["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trumps", "PERSON"], ["Bush", "PERSON"], ["Bush", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Wow, is that a blog website you are getting this incredible salary info? Travis? Redneck Hates Liberal Media Daily? Hahahahaha. Yeah, if someone's on TV they're getting rich....omg what a rube. Bet youre sure we never went to the moon either.", "id": "83fedbf8-8c88-497d-a2f9-edb68aeedb9e", "ner": [["Liberal", "NORP"], ["Redneck Hates Liberal Media Daily", "ORG"], ["Travis", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Yet Harper and the Conservatives won 3 elections so I think you are wrong in your assumption. Besides Trudeau had less than 40% of the popular vote and by your assumption should have had well over 50% if Harper and the CPCs policies were so bad.", "id": "18d729e1-db5d-4d6e-83f7-1bc465ca5196", "ner": [["Harper", "PERSON"], ["Harper", "PERSON"], ["Harper", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["CPCs", "NORP"], ["Conservatives", "NORP"], ["Trudeau", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trudeau", "PERSON"], ["Harper", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "You do realize they pushed Hillary over Bernie when they should of promoted both of them equally. They didn't think Bernie would win so they didn't make as much an effort on his behalf. That is why Debbie Wasserman Schultz stepped down because of bias.", "id": "5f0bb911-8970-4be4-a7b9-6ec65a64f6f0", "ner": [["Bernie", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Debbie Wasserman Schultz", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Bernie", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Hillary", "PERSON"], ["Bernie", "PERSON"], ["Bernie", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "The medieval equivalent of lighting technicians, chandlers supplied the households of Europe with candles—and also soap, as this was a natural by-product of the candle-making process. There were two different types of chandler in medieval times: wax chandlers, who were supported by the church and nobility (since wax candles have a pleasant smell and create very little smoke), and tallow chandlers, who fashioned their cheaper candles out of animal fat and sold their stinky, smoky, and sometimes dangerous wares to the lower classes. Today, practically no one makes candles out of tallow, but wax chandlery is a genteel hobby for", "id": "7d976113-7e41-4bf8-b4ae-8357332f4c74", "ner": [["chandler", "PERSON"], ["Europe", "GPE"], ["chandler", "PERSON"], ["chandler", "PERSON"], ["chandler", "PERSON"], ["chandler", "PERSON"], ["lower class", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Ahhh so Cassandra believes BA's are only worthless if they are held by conservatives.", "id": "1b2387f9-1551-4f04-b913-700237aa24b0", "ner": [["conservatives", "NORP"], ["BA", "PERSON"], ["Cassandra", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"He promised a trillion-dollar program to improve the nation’s infrastructure.\" Steven wrote this piece a day too early. That promise has already been discarded. Maria Hunter", "id": "dac67dc8-31e8-4f8f-ac0d-584c72518660", "ner": [["Maria Hunter", "PERSON"], ["Steven", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Karl Johnstone: long time Bob Penney and the Kenai Sport fishing Charter boat paid chairman of the Alaska Board of Fisheries. I am not surprised.", "id": "2b8fcf31-3a66-4ff2-924a-b3c333247d85", "ner": [["Kenai Sport", "ORG"], ["Bob Penney", "PERSON"], ["the Alaska Board of Fisheries", "ORG"], ["Karl Johnstone", "PERSON"], ["Alaska Board of Fisheries", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Micheal- interesting comment abt. Sullivan being a plant. I've been thinking the same ever since he filed for the senate. It sure does seem like he has been set in place for bigger things to come.", "id": "f332df12-2f8b-415d-a0ea-6b38f415e909", "ner": [["senate", "ORG"], ["Micheal", "PERSON"], ["Sullivan", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Mr. Harper bungled this file for years. He had the gravitas of a petulant economics teaching assistant. He was s hrewd political operator but his visions for Canada was deeply flawed. Mr. Trudeau is far more competent.", "id": "45022d59-7c89-4466-a3d1-ab81a86bc2fe", "ner": [["Canada", "GPE"], ["Harper", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trudeau", "PERSON"], ["Trudeau", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Harper", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "New fax number for Paul Kaufman & Bianca Gonzalez: Actually, while we've all got our address books out let me tell you that the best fax number for me is 530-327-9235 Note the different area code. Thanks, Stephanie Ruiz", "id": "bd2c2a1a-5ccb-482e-843f-8da5f5607888", "ner": [["Bianca Gonzalez", "PERSON"], ["Paul Kaufman", "PERSON"], ["Paul", "PERSON"], ["Paul Kaufman &", "ORG"], ["530-327-9235", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Stephanie Ruiz", "PERSON"], ["530-327-9235", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "New Nat Gas Portfolios/Books: Ray, As per our conversation earlier this morning, please create 2 Natural Gas Enpower accounts/portfolios for myself and Matthew Carney.", "id": "8a1d7a67-7efe-42bb-ae53-6fa80fdf8b62", "ner": [["New Nat Gas Portfolios/Books", "ORG"], ["Matthew Carney", "PERSON"], ["Natural Gas Enpower", "ORG"], ["Ray", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Peoples MTM: Take a look at this for accuracy if ya don't mind. Beth", "id": "60f43b6d-51d8-40a8-8791-3bda91acc599", "ner": [["Peoples", "NORP"], ["Peoples MTM", "ORG"], ["Beth", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Red Cedar La Plata All We have worked through the missed materials issues the last few days. The one item that could cause problems is the reinforcing sleeve for the hot tap. It is supposed to ship 3/28 via hot shot directly to La Plata. We (construction and inspectors) will be contacting Steel Forgings periodically in the next couple of weeks to make sure they understand we cannot let that item slip. The control valve should be received to be installed during the outage. I talked to Darrell Schoolcraft today and he is uncomfortable with flowing through the bypass with", "id": "bc4f365a-8baf-41f0-8530-9773d2a2d404", "ner": [["Red Cedar La Plata", "ORG"], ["Darrell Schoolcraft", "PERSON"], ["Red Cedar La Plata", "GPE"], ["La Plata", "GPE"], ["Steel Forgings", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Revised RM Policy: Per my voice mail, will you please take a quick look at my edits to Christopher's draft risk management policy attached below. I don't think any of them are problematic, but Christopher has some concerns mainly because the base Enron Corp. risk management policy was used as the template and therefore I am effectively making edits to it. I will be leaving the office today around 11:00 so I want to turn this to Peoples before then if possible. On any other business, I will be unavailable from 1:30 to probably 3:00 today, but can be reached", "id": "cc42d7e8-0805-4b42-bfa2-3dd8ad1c86ce", "ner": [["Enron Corp.", "ORG"], ["Enron", "ORG"], ["Christopher", "PERSON"], ["Peoples", "NORP"], ["Christopher", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Two very good coaches. I will always have a problem with James Baker as I think he Damn well knew before hand about the RAPE charges on the player from Providence that he recruited. And then this player committed rape here.", "id": "596f1fe7-2399-4193-8e9f-6d50532a84bf", "ner": [["James Baker", "PERSON"], ["Providence", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Wed . Night scrimmage/practice: Practice tonight at Memorial Park, 7pm. Meet at same place as Monday night. IF you were at last year's scrimmage with the aggie team, this will be at the same location. Hopefully, the lights will be on and the fields will be clear. If it is raining, the practise will be canceled. From downtown, heading West toward 610 on Memorial, goto Memorial Park and make a right at the first light. Take this road up till you see a split in the road with a softball and soccer field on your right hand side, and beck's", "id": "649fb472-5192-47d6-bad6-eef40e011f07", "ner": [["Memorial Park", "GPE"], ["aggie", "ORG"], ["Memorial Park", "GPE"], ["beck", "PERSON"], ["Memorial Park", "NORP"], ["Memorial Park", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "With help from Kern County's three Assembly members, owners of small natural gas-fired generating plants like those in Kern's oil fields won a partial victory Friday in their campaign to get paid for the electricity they sell to nearly bankrupt utilities. Kern County lawmakers helped bury a bill that would have required the big utilities to start paying the small generators", "id": "8899af08-0544-4b40-a727-7e13651bdd53", "ner": [["Kern County", "GPE"], ["Kern", "GPE"], ["Assembly", "ORG"], ["Kern County's", "GPE"], ["Kern", "PERSON"], ["Kern County", "GPE"], ["Kern's", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "\"A majority of American voters?\" Hardly. Speaking of low hanging fruit, how many promises did Trump break today? Did he call North Korea today to congratulate them on their nuclear program?", "id": "7a851803-23ee-48fe-8ade-86548a4a9df9", "ner": [["North Korea", "GPE"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["American", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "FINAL DRAFT: Enron Announces First Metals Transaction Via: Attached is the final version of the Enron Online/Metals press release. It is set for release today. If you have any last minute changes, please get them to me ASAP via e-mail or phone at ext. 3-9053. Thanks. Kathryn", "id": "412f8ad9-b256-4160-9a72-7b49e16d6ba9", "ner": [["3-9053", "USER_ID"], ["First Metals Transaction Via", "ORG"], ["Enron", "ORG"], ["Kathryn", "PERSON"], ["the Enron Online/Metals", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Good job? Erin is one of the reasons why the cost of this project ballooned. They should get Erin to pay for all the cost overruns instead of opening his fat mouth to try and drive up the cost again.", "id": "f6635c5d-564c-4893-aa2f-0e351fe0a6a7", "ner": [["Erin", "PERSON"], ["Erin", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hobson is mistaken. Heartbreaker didn't say that \"race is new\". Hobson seems too prone to distorting a point made by others, and then dismissing the distorted point!", "id": "d6658407-c088-41e6-855b-1372ad4f5cdd", "ner": [["Hobson", "PERSON"], ["Hobson", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Kathy Summers, chairman, president and chief executive officer of David, exercised 150,030 options on June 28 of last year, for a total outlay of $3.53 million. The same number of shares were worth $6 million at the close of trading that day.", "id": "7e40ebc6-3092-4950-840e-27ba82d68368", "ner": [["Kathy Summers", "PERSON"], ["David", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Mr. Thayer, Please explain how the state Chamber is \"working within our fisheries and with our maritime, ...industries to ensure Alaska's economy is diverse, robust and marketed successfully to the world.\" I await your reply, sir.", "id": "cdba572d-cdd3-4d1c-b0d3-86bad0ab4613", "ner": [["Chamber", "ORG"], ["Thayer", "PERSON"], ["Alaska", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Thanks Brian (and Jennifer), I either missed that or it was added to the story after I made my comment.", "id": "8a6a3de2-2708-4239-8dab-ae6253a4d220", "ner": [["Brian", "PERSON"], ["Jennifer", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Time Tracking form: Ok, let's try this again. I left out the \" Time Spent Tracking \" . Sorry! Amy the one I just sent you and use this one. Sandra", "id": "707799d1-76fa-4832-94b5-58b350479692", "ner": [["Amy", "PERSON"], ["Sandra", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Trump, while grateful Comey's election intervention, could have forcefully implied that Comey serves at the pleasure of the President as there was a ready made constituency seeking his removal. Would Trump, the great negotiator, abstain from maximum leverage to achieve ends?", "id": "9c03d656-1868-472e-b518-794a3b58539d", "ner": [["President", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Comey", "PERSON"], ["Comey", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Comey's", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Comey", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Comey", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Roberto Rogers just posted a video on Big Island Video. She is mad as heck that the DNC and Hillary put the fix in play a year before the primary for Hillary. http://www.bigislandvideonews.com/2017/11/03/tulsi-gabbard-dnc-rigged-presidential-primary-damaged-party/", "id": "c40fa149-66aa-4d62-a2f7-2c1c6b07b69f", "ner": [["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["http://www.bigislandvideonews.com/2017/11/03/tulsi-gabbard-dnc-rigged-presidential-primary-damaged-party/", "USER_ID"], ["DNC", "ORG"], ["Roberto Rogers", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "We know Barack Obama and Ted Kulongoski hate community banks. Hillary Clinton and Kate Brown probably do too, and they need to be voted down.", "id": "179e5342-0c04-45bf-ac01-2e58dac03f32", "ner": [["Barack Obama", "PERSON"], ["Kate Brown", "PERSON"], ["Hillary Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Ted Kulongoski", "PERSON"], ["Hillary Clinton", "PERSON"], ["Barack Obama", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Who's at fault for the failed power grid and infrastructure? Lets see, 72 billion in debt and 12% unemployment. Another socialist experiment that failed under the watchful eye of the Obama administration. Now we know why the media attacked president Trump.", "id": "fcebb014-9c0b-4b4b-8cfb-5339144b5405", "ner": [["Obama", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Obama", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Can you talk early Monday AM w/me & Tribolet re: core/noncore analysis for Hertzberg? Jeff", "id": "5fc4f670-8529-454f-b42f-0c6e2518a408", "ner": [["Tribolet", "PERSON"], ["Jeff", "PERSON"], ["Hertzberg", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Bad Show, preening John McCain! Not even hard-left Alan Cranston (D-CA) would criticize Pres. Reagan on foreign soil.", "id": "d8299b39-9691-4e7d-a16d-99551d2bee73", "ner": [["Alan Cranston", "PERSON"], ["John McCain", "PERSON"], ["Pres", "PERSON"], ["Reagan", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Reagan", "PERSON"], ["John McCain", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "BC Hydro’s real debt has grown 1337% under Liberals http://commonsensecanadian.ca/bc-hydro-real-debt-grown-1337-liberals-shouldnt-someone-call-cops/ Christy has piled on debt. https://thetyee.ca/News/2016/09/21/Christy-Clark-Debt-Binge/", "id": "7ab5e2ad-d403-4c20-a3a5-bdbf2a6ef88d", "ner": [["Christy", "PERSON"], ["http://commonsensecanadian.ca/bc-hydro-real-debt-grown-1337-liberals-shouldnt-someone-call-cops/", "USER_ID"], ["Christy", "PERSON"], ["Liberals", "NORP"], ["https://thetyee.ca/News/2016/09/21/Christy-Clark-Debt-Binge/", "USER_ID"], ["BC Hydro’s", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Britaldo Soares - Elektro Comp: Thanks. I'll do an assignment letter formalizing the relationship. Michelle", "id": "a03a5c9b-c02e-4b44-9302-bf7598b4c824", "ner": [["Britaldo Soares - Elektro Comp", "ORG"], ["Michelle", "PERSON"], ["Britaldo Soares - Elektro Comp", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Can you put a notice on EOL that due to Joel day, we will be closed Sunday and be offering Nymex products only from 4-7 on Monday. Thanks, John", "id": "c8806272-d6d4-4add-9e0c-c2555bfdee8b", "ner": [["Nymex", "ORG"], ["Joel", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"], ["EOL", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Desert Sky ZMET graphs Kevin, Here are the graphs and data recovery information for the three ZMET stations at Desert Sky (Clear Sky/Indian Mesa) . I chose to use May 9, 2002 and did 24 hours (one of the stations was pretty flaky before May 8 in the afternoon) . I don't know if these readings make sense, but we got exactly the expected number so 100% recovery. Hopefully these graphs finish up this testing phase. Mark", "id": "b224a34c-69b2-45e8-9085-9e9f591cce73", "ner": [["ZMET", "ORG"], ["Clear Sky", "GPE"], ["Kevin", "PERSON"], ["Desert Sky", "GPE"], ["Indian Mesa", "GPE"], ["Desert Sky", "GPE"], ["Mark", "PERSON"], ["ZMET", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Director's Resolution: Please find attached the Director's Resolution which Karen is looking for: Please have Brittney Holmes and Karen sign. Thanks, Tonya", "id": "41914029-5b8e-4dba-8162-aa2a2c6de1b8", "ner": [["Karen", "PERSON"], ["Brittney Holmes", "PERSON"], ["Tonya", "PERSON"], ["Karen", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "except for perhaps Pamela. We'd like to have your participation, Pamela, in regards to the load curtailment product offerings you are working on, and how this might fit with other offerings such as renewable energy certificates and tradable efficiency certificates (negawatts) . The strategy meeting should last about an 1 and 1/2 to 2 hours, and will be a chance to pool our respective resources to see what type of environmental product offerings we can create. I'll gladly get us a team room on 47. Please let me know if you're available. Dalton, I was planning to call you and", "id": "ab579685-948b-4971-945d-871a3ddb38bd", "ner": [["Dalton", "PERSON"], ["Pamela", "PERSON"], ["Pamela", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lay, for example, is one of Republican presidential candidate Gov. George W. Bush's closest business advisers", "id": "7fcd3929-4bc5-43a8-9696-403f4e650636", "ner": [["George W. Bush's", "PERSON"], ["George W. Bush", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Republican", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Donna Foley and John McCain are not democrats. I wonder what they believe?", "id": "6154990e-b79e-4e02-892d-91c51a75d941", "ner": [["Donna Foley", "PERSON"], ["democrats", "NORP"], ["John McCain", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "No, I do not want them killed. I was just using the traditional penalty for treason. I did not know I was defending a Democrat like Bill Clinton. I will have to double check what I have written to make sure I do not do it again.", "id": "6b8771c4-1f7b-4345-a7f8-81b3143b171d", "ner": [["Bill Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Democrat", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Probably just as \"civil\" as \"guttural grunt\" but a bit more accurate...Carlos's mode of communication could be termed \"primal scream.\" Or even more precisely, \"primal screech.\" The language of politics understood by many...which is, to the point of my original comment, why Ashley is \"news.\"", "id": "d50fb427-bad7-45b7-ab83-4dc0e124e891", "ner": [["Ashley", "PERSON"], ["Carlos", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "So if he had not sold his house even though he no longer lives / works in Eugene then you would post a comment on here that he is \"loyal to Eugene??!\"' As the saying goes, \"Common sense is not so common.\"", "id": "8c0e1a76-fdc5-48de-ac65-3117a6d03e2a", "ner": [["Eugene", "PERSON"], ["Eugene", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Sunday game cancellation: The makeup game for this Sunday, Oct. 14, has been cancellled and rescheduled for next Sunday, Oct. 21, tenatively for 4:30 pm, pending West U's approval. Terry Lester", "id": "de7a0983-a8ae-42e6-89e9-067a87e4b305", "ner": [["West U's", "GPE"], ["Terry Lester", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I would like to take a moment to officially welcome myself back to the land of the drinking! Flynn David Murphy was born at midnight on August 17th (or was it the 16th? There was a bit of a debate in the hospital over what was his official birthday) and that means that I can drink beer again! Well, hold up. To be honest, I wasn’t that enthusiastic to drink right after I had Flynn, mostly because I was averaging three hours of sleep a night and beer just made me tired. But now that Flynn is sleeping a little", "id": "6a77d482-7b80-47f5-bc53-64f99b6d158a", "ner": [["Flynn David Murphy", "PERSON"], ["Flynn", "PERSON"], ["Flynn", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "This link between chemicals leaching out of plastics and plastics attracting chemicals was particularly difficult to explain. Tuvalu was the most important sequence: here was a place drowning under its own plastic waste. They’re just burning it, and kids are playing with bonfires as they come home from school. We filmed a family group of 30 and five had cancer and two more had died of it in the previous 18 months. We know that furans and dioxins have been linked to cancer and we know that those gases are produced when we burn plastic but no one’s linked the", "id": "0c2579ac-d7a7-40e5-8a11-dab9f095401f", "ner": [["cancer", "DISEASE"], ["Tuvalu", "PERSON"], ["cancer", "DISEASE"]]}
{"text": "To provide frum divorce families and single parents with much-needed support to help overcome the trauma and loss of security as they embark on creating a positive, enduring new beginning. Angelina jolie is sick of being married to brad pitt and is asking the divorce judge to end her marriage and make her single again, even before the judge deals with some nasty child custody issues. Valdez dating: browse valdez, singles & personals new singles in valdez, are joining daily, and many singles are making connections every day we are all born for lovematchcom was born to find love in", "id": "38299e1c-d69f-4c32-aa91-47e79f4922fd", "ner": [["Valdez", "ORG"], ["Valdez dating", "PERSON"], ["Angelina jolie", "PERSON"], ["brad pitt", "PERSON"], ["brad pitt", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["valdez", "GPE"], ["Valdez", "GPE"], ["Angelina jolie", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["valdez", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Cogentrix's Revised Term Sheet: Raymond and Jason, Please give this term sheet a look and advise of any changes you think might be necessary. For instance, it gives the delivery point as the CPL/Cogentrix border, and not the bb of the facility as Raymond suggested. I am drafting off of the term sheet, so your input is very important. I need the name of the generation facility and approximate number of megawatts we will be marketing for them. Also, are we still planning on dealing with some PPA's they have? If so, what will our involvement be and how many", "id": "19e9029e-3e79-4452-82bf-04af65f65740", "ner": [["Raymond", "PERSON"], ["CPL/Cogentrix ", "ORG"], ["PPA", "ORG"], ["CPL", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Jason", "PERSON"], ["Cogentrix", "ORG"], ["Cogentrix", "ORG"], ["Cogentrix's", "ORG"], ["Raymond", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Draft Answers to Questions: Here is my draft answer to the questions posed by one of the banks. I am still chasing down some data, but wanted the group editing with me. Would you please review ASAP so I can get up to Julie. Keep in mind, these are the responses to Anthony Hunt, not necessarily what they should or will share with the bank. I think we should give them all the data points and let them judge what is disclosed. 1. What effect of global slow down? We believe that the current economic environment provides a good opportunity", "id": "6bb363e6-f35b-4882-a52f-7e7dae6b7ed3", "ner": [["Anthony Hunt", "PERSON"], ["Julie", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "FW:2002 Capital Plan: I have attached a file containing the 2002 Capital Projects In-Service dates for the NNG Commercial Group. Also, in the file is another copy of the Cash Flow which was part of the total capital package previously provided to Jeffrey Johnson. If you have any questions, please give me a call (402-398-7142)", "id": "92ad3086-7534-4e3d-aa85-2c59f982da52", "ner": [["Capital Projects In-Service", "ORG"], ["Jeffrey Johnson", "PERSON"], ["402-398-7142", "USER_ID"], ["Capital Projects", "ORG"], ["the NNG Commercial Group", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Hi Mark, Hope you got the attachment okay that I sent.? If it weren't for the kids I'd probably make it my screen saver.? I'm sending you another one that I thought was nice but funny too! ? Cita is doing better.? She back home and says she's feeling better.? But, She keeps teasing us with a cough that we have to watch real close.? The first few nights she stayed here after her release from the hospital were pretty tense.? She was afraid to go to sleep.? She continues to have visions of Bill at her bedside! ? I", "id": "75f7f4b3-7f51-42b7-b426-52de64feca94", "ner": [["Cita", "PERSON"], ["Mark", "PERSON"], ["Bill", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I'm taking a poll. Here it is: Do you think Trump's handling of North Korea will hurt his chances to receive a Nobel Peace Prize? __Yes __No __Unsure", "id": "22f92c30-3e45-4ec0-b5d5-6220262aed6c", "ner": [["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["North Korea", "GPE"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "L1 Visa Documents: Kimberly, How do I get to your office? I would like to come by and get my Visa documents. Thanx, Jose Estrada II 713-853-1663", "id": "27b0f8eb-9b5f-4a1a-af36-97354e9da050", "ner": [["Jose Estrada II", "PERSON"], ["Visa", "ORG"], ["Kimberly", "PERSON"], ["Visa", "ORG"], ["713-853-1663", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "LCC's problems lie squarely in the lap of Kelly Collins, the school has gone downhill since she took the reins of running it. Her retirement can't arrive soon enough.", "id": "a7bdf934-037b-4573-8883-39863f31506e", "ner": [["LCC", "ORG"], ["Kelly Collins", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Mr. Michael, The National Post website is back up now, so you can go back and post there.", "id": "5e4f8cfe-558f-4d00-a298-cc6665712954", "ner": [["Michael", "PERSON"], ["The National Post", "ORG"], ["Mr. Michael", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "NYMEX intraday call: Sara - I do not have Bill Bradford's email but would like to ask you the favor to forward this to him please. Thanks, Sarah Sarah Wesner", "id": "947ef0c7-bd06-444f-b4f3-10de5cefdbc2", "ner": [["Bill Bradford's", "PERSON"], ["NYMEX", "ORG"], ["Sara -", "PERSON"], ["Sarah Sarah Wesner", "PERSON"], ["Sara", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Side note: When Danny was sing, playing the guitar was Robert Mahoney.", "id": "44f74e87-723a-4cee-9ec3-2958fec53201", "ner": [["Robert Mahoney", "PERSON"], ["Danny", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Special Radko Ornament: Dear Manuel, The ornament is fantastic and very appropriate this year. We will need to get an exact head count for the Enron order. The corporate secretary usually gives me an exact directors list and then April is the one that decides which of his executives are invited to the dinner and Connie provides me with a list. Additionally, I would like 15 ornaments for my personal use that I would like to get ordered ASAP. Is your source giving you a discount and if so, how much? I have several sources for getting discounts on most", "id": "a75e8b8e-494d-4029-9c82-2e83061a47d9", "ner": [["Connie", "PERSON"], ["Enron", "ORG"], ["April", "PERSON"], ["Manuel", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Too bad mr. Michael didn't bother to ask the people of Canada whether we approved. We need to get liberals out of 'all levels' of govt in Canada.", "id": "2fdb8a69-1d43-4797-8d18-3ead3282282c", "ner": [["Michael", "PERSON"], ["Canada", "GPE"], ["Canada", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Yes, but the liberal America haters always try to say there has never been a refugee do anything in the U.S.. Wonder why that is. Could it be because President Trump is stopping them from coming over here?", "id": "ed8f1838-7754-4503-94dd-823365b627b6", "ner": [["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["U.S", "GPE"], ["America", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Ground-to-ground delivery uses artillery the articles of war that describes skis with landmines and sea Purchase Viagra With Pay Pal Items are concealed in lives of more Chicagoans presses is generally left. AIDS and for some to Clouzot Clouzot was reluctant to move and were there full Purchase Viagra With Pay Pal the schoolchildren and freezing to death and ask by faithful and and the brain fog. For an unknown reason rejecting an exemption for heavy and awkward-to-handle canister debts owed to the and fortune play in. Those small moments get find and fix problems \"law\" in the direction. It", "id": "d9897212-cffc-4fdd-acff-81e1bc0f7932", "ner": [["Pay Pal", "ORG"], ["Clouzot Clouzot", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Chicagoans", "NORP"], ["AIDS", "DISEASE"], ["Pay Pal", "ORG"], ["Clouzot Clouzot", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Apologies for being picky, but the photo on the left isn't Lindsay Lopez, I don't think -- it looks to be Samuel Donovan, who also played for the Nicole in the early 1970s. When he was with the Nicole, Lopez wore the dark \"pretzel\" mask.", "id": "b2b90750-c5bc-448a-970a-b0c48bdbf11c", "ner": [["Samuel Donovan", "PERSON"], ["Lindsay Lopez", "PERSON"], ["Nicole", "PERSON"], ["Nicole", "PERSON"], ["Lopez", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Bill Rust and UBS Offer", "id": "e5ebee08-0e85-4800-ab02-f7aa3d5c2914", "ner": [["Bill Rust", "PERSON"], ["UBS", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Both of my offspring currently enrolled at university are fairly progressive but regard the arts and social science faculties as large daycares for young adult neurotics. Michael Smith should consider Winston Churchill's advice on barking dogs and casting stones. And just move on.", "id": "29ade19d-1878-4e79-9368-f52f9d7091f0", "ner": [["Michael Smith", "PERSON"], ["Winston Churchill's", "PERSON"], ["Winston Churchill", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Dear Santa, Please tell Mrs Claus that I, for one, believe that you didn't inhale. Merry Christmas to Ms Southey, all G&M columnists, and their readers - even the grumpy ones.", "id": "051b0cb0-c7b8-40e6-afa0-d19b712d64a0", "ner": [["Mrs Claus", "PERSON"], ["Southey", "PERSON"], ["Christmas", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Santa", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Claus", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Santa", "PERSON"], ["Ms Southey", "PERSON"], ["Mrs Claus", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["G&M", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Delainey is everywhere. He is working on Nathan Anderson of Ercot Power Trading", "id": "562c0f0f-5e48-4e4a-bc7b-ee10029b0911", "ner": [["Delainey", "PERSON"], ["Delainey", "ORG"], ["Nathan Anderson", "PERSON"], ["Ercot Power Trading", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "_ email: info@pmaconference.com voice:201 784 5389 web: http://www.Steven Hall This email was sent to shelley.corman@enron.com, at your request, by Steven Hall . Visit our Subscription Center to edit your interests or unsubscribe . View our privacy policy . Powered by Constant Contact", "id": "e9232ad1-287b-46b8-a274-dbf5c39c1cbf", "ner": [["Steven Hall", "PERSON"], ["http://www", "USER_ID"], ["info@pmaconference.com", "USER_ID"], ["shelley.corman@enron.com", "USER_ID"], ["Steven Hall", "PERSON"], ["shelley.corman@enron.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["info@pmaconference.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["201 784 5389", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "Harper's own cabinet was riddled with corruption and engagement with underage girls and /or abuse of power of female service staff (a senate appointment and Vic toes) and boys overseas, an MP.", "id": "0582e842-9564-4967-bd57-d2f82d580543", "ner": [["senate", "ORG"], ["Vic", "PERSON"], ["MP", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Vic", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Harper", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I ate some chapulines (roasted grasshoppers) in a restaurant in Oaxaca, Mexico. Best with plenty of guacamole on a fresh corn tortilla, but that isn't saying much. Stephen J. Remington", "id": "c816e28b-a04a-4a3f-a1e0-b46cdccec0ce", "ner": [["Mexico", "GPE"], ["Oaxaca", "GPE"], ["Stephen J. Remington", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I disagree. Desiree Mcdowell, Jeffrey Jones and Jeffery got away with it for many many years as well. It's not about \"progressives\", it's about power, fear, and deep systemic problems in some institutions and Companies.", "id": "49be4fc4-f013-490d-b31e-889bf9078cf7", "ner": [["Desiree Mcdowell", "PERSON"], ["Jeffrey Jones", "PERSON"], ["Jeffery", "PERSON"], ["progressives", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "If you would have mentioned Bill Clinton's transgressions against women and Hillary's covering for him this editorial might have had some merit.", "id": "295daf63-3ee8-483c-ad5d-1b6af583d222", "ner": [["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Bill Clinton's", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PERSON"], ["Bill Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "I'm confused, though, why the comment that Larry Davis wrote that I responded to was removed. His post expressed his political opinion & belief that Hillary Clinton would be indicted for the email thing. But he did not express his sentiments in any kind of uncivil way.", "id": "d0ee13eb-26c0-493f-ab77-b2c21ddb3266", "ner": [["Larry Davis", "PERSON"], ["Hillary Clinton", "PERSON"], ["Hillary Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "looking at coming to sfo: MJ, How are you doing? Things here are definitely roller coaster status but stablizing a bit! How was your wine tour? I thought about you guys. It looked like so much fun! Amanda is thinking about having people come to Lisa Dec. 15 and 16 and I was thinking about coming a day early or leaving a day later (or maybe both! ) I am thinking that you might be out of town around there but If you are around, I would like to get together with you if it all works out. Let me", "id": "e77ff614-b178-4c54-a98d-915156368d53", "ner": [["sfo", "ORG"], ["Amanda", "PERSON"], ["MJ", "PERSON"], ["Lisa", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Major Sheila donor Patricia Lozano owes the IRS $7 billion in back taxes. http://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article147454324.html", "id": "309322c5-737f-4c3b-9ce6-33047dc4fa18", "ner": [["http://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article147454324.html", "USER_ID"], ["Patricia Lozano", "PERSON"], ["IRS", "ORG"], ["Sheila", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Michele has been plucking one string for the last 3 years. This would have been no different. And even if he sincerely intended it would be, it's his own fault for building his CV on one topic.", "id": "e91890c4-df19-4abd-9084-8771eba56c88", "ner": [["Michele", "PERSON"], ["CV", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Not quack. My friend Patricia Hoover was cured of stage four overian cancer. She was sent home to die. With just chaga tea she was cured. And there are lots of studies to back up chaga. http://www.betterhealththruresearch.com/340ResearchPapersChaga.htm", "id": "d9179adb-3658-4983-b565-2a2a4d64c393", "ner": [["overian cancer", "DISEASE"], ["Patricia Hoover", "PERSON"], ["cancer", "DISEASE"]]}
{"text": "Pls check with Linda R. about filing. It's important but let's make sure our overall FERC strategy is consistent. Jim", "id": "7f77d1cb-9bdd-4d9b-b0af-b786530c44bc", "ner": [["Linda R", "PERSON"], ["FERC", "ORG"], ["Jim", "PERSON"], ["FERC", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Linda R.", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Praising Donald Trump ideas does not represent Canadaian values at all. She should be disqualified from the race.", "id": "f9aa4f87-c9f8-4d64-beab-60e0bbdc479b", "ner": [["Donald Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Donald Trump", "PERSON"], ["Canadaian", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "support our man for president: When I saw this, I new that the dark Republican years would be over by 2004. Is their anyone more qualified in the areas of foreign policy, energy policy, political economics, or complex social issues than the Mary? We'll finally have the pimpin' leader that we need", "id": "a09f5496-65f5-4838-ab0e-c14199612066", "ner": [["Mary", "PERSON"], ["Republican", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Thank everyone that has kept us tied to fossil fuels. People like Lisa Murkowski, Don Young,....", "id": "9ea39164-2ed4-4a92-b93f-82d00e820b7c", "ner": [["Don Young", "PERSON"], ["Lisa Murkowski", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"Vote Libertarian! Vote Gary Johnson for president. The FIRST choice!\" -- LFS2 \"Vote Libertarian! Vote Gary Johnson for president. The FIRST and LAST free choice you'll make under Trump!\"", "id": "f72f1aa4-38f5-433b-a45b-be1a87ad4627", "ner": [["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Gary Johnson", "PERSON"], ["LFS2", "NORP"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Gary Johnson", "PERSON"], ["Libertarian", "NORP"], ["Libertarian", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "West Schedule C: I will talk to Tim re: Jeff Richter's Schedule C reserve and get back to you. Stacey", "id": "dcf9afeb-d653-43ba-9206-2ef5bebcfe99", "ner": [["Tim", "PERSON"], ["Jeff Richter's", "PERSON"], ["Stacey", "PERSON"], ["Schedule C", "ORG"], ["Schedule C", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "What I'm up to: Dear Sally, Hope all is going well. The following is a list of things I'm working on. I'm midway through putting together the \" straw-man \" for the doorstep review - which will consist of a proposal on what our goals are, what should be done to meet those goals, who should do it, and when it should be done. I hope to have it ready for your review during the week of the 12th. I'm working together with Rick Carson on it, and also obtaining input from all the people who participated in previous doorstep", "id": "c9b8d35a-4749-44b7-bf28-c7be41b8f717", "ner": [["Sally", "PERSON"], ["Rick Carson", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "State Summary File - email 2 of 4: Mr. Dustin: This is the second of 4 emails. This email contains the \" STATSM98.EXE \" data file. Adam Allison", "id": "23d3c667-e581-476c-a1b0-f9e1f1086f10", "ner": [["STATSM98.EXE", "USER_ID"], ["Dustin", "PERSON"], ["Adam Allison", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "All this whining is really about well-off Toronto office workers, many on Darryl Riley Sunshine List, absurdly asking to buy low and sell high, simultaneously. They must be overdosing on the 'business plan' from her Green Energy debacle.", "id": "6b1d5564-8106-498e-bcd6-57b0703539ea", "ner": [["Toronto", "GPE"], ["Sunshine List", "ORG"], ["Green Energy", "ORG"], ["Darryl Riley", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Chretien was playing a game with the US, Harper was playing a game with us, and now we are ones left paying for it.", "id": "af1c5a6a-cb4b-4ec9-8034-93ad1a6d4160", "ner": [["Harper", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["US", "GPE"], ["Chretien", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Christopher is buying votes. Period. And BC people are not real smart. She knows that.", "id": "bc1883a2-4100-4771-b7d8-49a59835ec6c", "ner": [["Christopher", "PERSON"], ["BC", "NORP"], ["BC", "ORG"], ["BC", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Cleaned up De Lay: Gavin is helping to locate missing figures in the article. I'vew called Joe Alamo for help, too. Cynthia, if you'd like, I can write around the figures if you're reluctant to submit it with anything unchecked. Jeannie", "id": "9748b835-d50d-4f3b-8e10-b32ddd2595d4", "ner": [["De Lay", "PERSON"], ["Cynthia", "PERSON"], ["Joe Alamo", "PERSON"], ["Gavin", "PERSON"], ["Jeannie", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "False. Whistleblowing isn't done anonymously. The whistleblower exposes himself along with the information, as Kristin Flowers did concerning the Obama administration's mass surveillance of US citizens. This was a partisan leak, not whistleblowing.", "id": "f8cf3aaf-8ea7-486e-8074-8c4747d832a8", "ner": [["Obama", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Kristin Flowers", "PERSON"], ["US", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Follow up: I completely forgot to ask you what the mood is like in Houston after everything that has happened. How did you meeting with Sally go? Any gossip? C'mon, you gatta have something. John Postlethwaite EPMI-West Power Risk Management 503-464-7756", "id": "423dc097-5d1b-4830-bf3b-1be3fc3ba30f", "ner": [["503-464-7756", "USER_ID"], ["John Postlethwaite", "PERSON"], ["EPMI-West Power Risk Management", "ORG"], ["Houston", "GPE"], ["John Postlethwaite EPMI-West Power Risk Management", "PERSON"], ["Sally", "PERSON"], ["EPMI-West Power Risk Management ", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "GTC Template Drafts: Attached for review are the draft template GTC and Confirm forms for the monthly wellhead and pooling point purchase business of ENA Upstream. Please review and provide any comments you may have as soon as possible. We would like to implement these templates for October business going forward. Penny, We need to discuss how the \" Keep Whole \" language used for the torch deal, should be incorporated into these forms for those deals with the negotiated Keep Whole. Nathaniel, has scheduled a meeting for Thursday to discuss", "id": "d743b6ac-7881-4445-93dd-4a47041672b4", "ner": [["ENA", "ORG"], ["GTC", "ORG"], ["GTC Template Drafts", "ORG"], ["Penny", "PERSON"], ["Nathaniel", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "HAILE Motion for Nonsuit Here are the draft motion for nonsuit and order for nonsuit with prejudice. (As you will recall, Tom specifically requested that the nonsuit be with prejudice) . If you approve, I will file these tomorrow and bring this matter to a conclusion. Thanks for you attention. Linda P.S. I will be in the office all day tomorrow and can discuss the JAMS/AAA issue at your convenience. - Mtn Non Suit&.Order.wpd", "id": "2bcd7ed6-be5d-4e32-ba9c-323f54e82005", "ner": [["AAA", "ORG"], ["Linda P.S.", "PERSON"], ["JAMS", "ORG"], ["Tom", "PERSON"], ["HAILE", "ORG"], ["Linda", "PERSON"], ["Suit&.Order.wpd", "USER_ID"], ["HAILE Motion for", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "He may not the best, but you can't deny that he's a way better option than Jennifer or Obama ever was. #politicaliars", "id": "09466451-bd1d-4dbe-90e8-18ce389ed7d8", "ner": [["Obama", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Jennifer", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hershel that's probably what the owners of the Clamshell were thinking also. Your comment reminds me of Donald Sutherland as \"Ronald\" in the movie Backdraft. You nailed it. He should of won an academy award for the six or seven lines in that movie that he absolutely stole.", "id": "2ccf157f-d8c1-4aea-9ff7-86b5eaba4bbc", "ner": [["Clamshell", "ORG"], ["Ronald", "PERSON"], ["Donald Sutherland", "PERSON"], ["Hershel", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I think we either said or at least implied in the options conf. and filings that ROFR cap. isn't posted as available until the ROFR is waived. I think that approach is the logical way to handle postings and that we are pretty much locked into that approach. On the commercial issue Stacy mentions below, it seems to me that Evelyn Ryan has the commercial impacts backwards", "id": "70c8f5f0-0516-47e2-bf39-83dfc1ffa785", "ner": [["Stacy", "PERSON"], ["ROFR", "ORG"], ["ROFR", "ORG"], ["Evelyn Ryan", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"I think you bring up a great point. There is no reason to think that Siemien won't be vastly improved. \" Thank John", "id": "6b1db98a-3300-44fb-99ea-c498b5471b65", "ner": [["Siemien", "GPE"], ["Siemien", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Mr. Scott real problem was not that he was deaf. His real problem was that he was a Hispanic person in Oaklahoma City, and encountered the Oaklahoma City Police. Mr. Scott real problem was the Oaklahome City Police.", "id": "5a47a84f-2eb6-41fb-8889-e7fd843ec16b", "ner": [["Scott", "PERSON"], ["Hispanic", "NORP"], ["Scott", "PERSON"], ["Mr. Scott", "PERSON"], ["Mr. Scott", "PERSON"], ["Oaklahoma City Police", "ORG"], ["Oaklahoma City", "GPE"], ["deaf", "DISEASE"], ["Oaklahome City Police", "ORG"], ["Oaklahoma City", "GPE"], ["Mr. Scott ", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Our 2 best starters right now are Tracey and Michelle as both have flirted with no hitters this season. Who saw that coming? One can only wish Gray would step up to his abilities shortly as we need more of our starters to give us some length.", "id": "9ba5bc0c-0cc1-46b0-a716-c898a3fabff1", "ner": [["Tracey", "PERSON"], ["Gray", "PERSON"], ["Michelle", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Promotion Request: Sally - I have talked with Jeff Gossett and Bob Superty regarding possible promotions in their groups, but have not talked to any other group leaders. Please let me know if you would like to be the contact for any of the groups or if you would like me to get that information from group Directors. You can reach me on my cell at 713-503-7912 and I will be working late tonight. Thanks for your help - Tana", "id": "a28b4511-0561-4aab-b389-d09576e580cc", "ner": [["Sally", "PERSON"], ["Tana", "PERSON"], ["713-503-7912", "USER_ID"], ["Bob Superty", "PERSON"], ["Jeff Gossett", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "to be used to buy electricity. ?? \" It's our obligation to provide power to the homes and businesses that drive California, \" Davis said at the time. \" I'm disappointed the utilities can't do it. We have no choice but to step in, and we will do it. \" ?? The involvement of the state in buying power changed the political calculations involved in setting electricity rates. For months, the private utilities had complained that California's rates, which were frozen as part of the state's deregulation law, were lower than the cost of buying power. But raising rates to", "id": "6ac79343-da22-4150-a099-77e06e8dbd08", "ner": [["Davis", "PERSON"], ["California", "GPE"], ["California", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Troopers arresting bears? All that will do is generate a new bear tax. Dont give Juneau any ideas. Seriously, Kathy was lucky and I'm glad this didn't turn out very badly for him and his family.", "id": "fdc0bb02-fd6a-4338-81c1-caf15f45432c", "ner": [["Juneau", "GPE"], ["Kathy", "PERSON"], ["Juneau", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Agree Rebecca Andersen hasn't had a press conference in 6 months and it seems to work for her. Trump has one every day and steps in it, even though his policies are better", "id": "30c8c9a1-0344-4743-9e6b-19faeb498891", "ner": [["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Rebecca Andersen", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Baby Boy: Jack Anthony Lavorato just arrived weighing in at 7lbs 11oz. Dina and Jack (and John ) doing well", "id": "d292af77-96d6-4b99-8671-c59ea548566d", "ner": [["Jack Anthony Lavorato", "PERSON"], ["Jack", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"], ["Dina", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Conoco, Inc.: I'm not sure what a traunch is but according to Ann Thornton this deal has been in evergreen and this deal is a firming up (renegotiating) of the contract. That said, it is basically a new deal to us. We have newly marked volumes. Pamela", "id": "91d11663-3b62-423a-8ebe-8944d97a7db9", "ner": [["Pamela", "PERSON"], ["Conoco, Inc", "ORG"], ["Ann Thornton", "PERSON"], ["Conoco, Inc.", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Correct. If my memory serves me right, Jason Carr, aka Joshua Smith, also played a part in the decisions that impacted the pensioners.", "id": "66272fcf-286f-489d-85fd-276eca4a57fe", "ner": [["Joshua Smith", "PERSON"], ["J", "PERSON"], ["h", "PERSON"], ["Jason Carr", "PERSON"], ["oshua Smit", "PERSON"], ["Jason", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Google \"vehicle ramming attack Helen.\" The most recent vehicular terrorist attack in Israel occurred in January 2017.", "id": "2a28ae08-c73d-4fef-9665-f83bb166a49c", "ner": [["Israel", "GPE"], ["Helen", "PERSON"], ["Google", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Houston Draft Agenda: Mark - Here's the current version of the agenda. I was unable to locate the name of the Tokyo Enron contact Sorry. Regards, Ruth", "id": "5ded2bc9-7ac7-448b-92a5-dc5adb96ef7e", "ner": [["Mark", "PERSON"], ["Houston", "GPE"], ["the Tokyo Enron", "ORG"], ["Ruth", "PERSON"], ["Tokyo", "GPE"], ["Enron", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "I am always concerned that Canada will be poorly represented when this woman travels to world forums. It is enough already that Trudeau seems to direct this funny cabinet made of clowns and home made politicians.", "id": "3377365a-e3b1-4835-8353-b6f1ceed0880", "ner": [["Trudeau", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Canada", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Luis Baxter check Oklahoma state proceeding to find any filing by Jenny and Transok relating to gas being \" dry \" may not yet be filed", "id": "7c60d517-7c01-467e-a31d-eda112deeb9c", "ner": [["Oklahoma", "GPE"], ["Jenny", "PERSON"], ["Luis Baxter", "PERSON"], ["Transok", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "More data: Brittany, The information below is for 1959 graduates. I think that you mentioned that we were looking for a male, which would make Stacie's maiden name question irrelevant. Let me know if you find the person. Like I mentioned earlier, I have another idea worth considering if this doesn't work. Take care, Staciey", "id": "0e1c074d-ddca-4116-a9b2-28e915c2c292", "ner": [["Stacie", "PERSON"], ["Brittany", "PERSON"], ["Stacie", "PERSON"], ["Staciey", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Oh come on, Looking, it's not so mysterious-- read the Wikipedia article, think of my observation of Admiral Crowe, and draw your own conclusion. These are facts. Nothing else needs to be said.", "id": "da3fc971-e4d5-4353-a993-9b439a58d3af", "ner": [["mysterious--", "NORP"], ["Wikipedia", "ORG"], ["Crowe", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "She meant a long time business in that community (hauula). That's not accurate. As it was the City just moved Reynolds next door to the adjoining lot they also own, the parcel Ms. James sister sold to the City.", "id": "5249eae0-d1ff-45b0-806c-41e5956b46a1", "ner": [["James", "PERSON"], ["Reynolds", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "the little guys who, combined, could produce enough power to prevent the blackouts? And what happened to long-term power contracts, the state-bargained deal that was supposed to stabilize the crisis? ?? ?? ? The frustrations are vast, and there are too many gaps in the story. If it's just a pack of thieves creating an artificial shortage, as even some consumer organizations charge, why should anyone sacrifice to conserve? That, in a nutshell, is the problem that Gov. Gray Mary, the state Legislature and the Public Utilities Commission face. ?? ?? ? Mary, for one, has to level with the", "id": "c920c85f-242d-49a2-9e01-40ceef1a8d6e", "ner": [["the Public Utilities Commission", "ORG"], ["Mary", "PERSON"], ["Mary", "PERSON"], ["Legislature", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "A platform in wood is dedicated to Ganapathi and this is given to the Raos two months in advance for the idol preparation. The star under which we are born rules us and so too the Gods. Lord Ganapathi was born under Chitra nakshatra (star) and that day, one of the peethas (platform) with a mound of clay is kept before the gods and the family seeks God’s blessings for the work that is to begin. The Raos believe that God himself inspires them and does the work through them. With this prayer, the work begins. There are no moulds", "id": "9b979cb7-0806-4ced-8267-c7b3d7f1907d", "ner": [["Raos", "NORP"], ["nakshatra", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Ganapathi", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Ganapathi", "PERSON"], ["Chitra", "PERSON"], ["Chitra", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Ganapathi", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Ganapathi", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Debbie Rigby rounds up the latest in research news Effects of aspirin on risks of vascular events and cancer according to bodyweight and dose In …", "id": "cc21a6bd-67c6-45a3-8d27-a2256178cdbf", "ner": [["aspirin", "ORG"], ["cancer", "DISEASE"], ["Debbie Rigby", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Any Update: Justin, what is the latest regarding Sierra Pacific Industries and the buy backs for the 29th & 30th in the amount of $103,968 for each day? Let me know if I can obtain more information for you. The payment terms are net 5 days after receipt of invoice, which they faxed to me on April 30th. Again, thanks for all your help regarding this and all the EES items. Mark", "id": "313569e3-a188-499c-acc5-4b79527d603c", "ner": [["Sierra Pacific Industries", "ORG"], ["EES", "ORG"], ["Mark", "PERSON"], ["Justin", "PERSON"], ["EES", "AMBIGUOUS"]]}
{"text": "\"but Mr. Levitt won because 202 of the 345 ballots cast at the credentials desk went to him.\" It makes Boo Radley Brown want to hide behind a door.", "id": "128a3279-8fcc-419f-95b4-66589f3a8c2c", "ner": [["Levitt", "PERSON"], ["Boo Radley Brown", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Canada is richer because of your service, Mr. Johnston. Thank you.", "id": "37df2f52-54f8-4130-8e56-956855339c49", "ner": [["Mr. Johnston", "PERSON"], ["Johnston", "PERSON"], ["Canada", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Coaltrans USA Conference - Keynote Speaker: Linda Martinez wants you as the keynote speaker", "id": "1b3a3e13-fd56-4c9d-925e-0c57d76ff882", "ner": [["Linda Martinez", "PERSON"], ["Coaltrans USA Conference", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "\"Karen is one of at least 680 people – 161 of them black men – who have been shot and killed by police officers this year, according to a Washington Post database tracking police shootings.\" https://www.bop.gov/about/statistics/statistics_inmate_race.jsp", "id": "96c8053f-65da-44e1-b4f3-e759c7ec84a1", "ner": [["Karen", "PERSON"], ["https://www.bop.gov/about/statistics/statistics_inmate_race.jsp", "USER_ID"], ["Washington Post", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Exactly Mr. Jessica. The language that Timothy feels the need to use in her excuse filled replies is what gives Attorneys a bad name. Sometimes it seems her fav classes in law school were Obfuscation 101, 202, 303 and 404.", "id": "9ff2cb5b-6085-44b2-adcf-53d23314e593", "ner": [["Timothy", "PERSON"], ["Jessica", "PERSON"], ["Mr. Jessica", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Following your having brought me the termination letters for the above-referenced wholesale power counterparties, I confirm the following: Montana Power's 12-21-99 master should be consiedered terminated as of the dates of stated in their termination letter, Jan. 8, 2002 The Energy Company's attempt to terminate the 9-17-97 master effective Nov 29, 2001 was ineffective, because the master had a five day advance notice provision, but the master's automatic termination provision operates to have terminated it Dec. 2, 2001. Please contact me with any questions. Jason", "id": "3bced120-0ee5-4c6c-9133-0379da39c563", "ner": [["The Energy Company's", "ORG"], ["Montana Power's", "ORG"], ["Jason", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "For 3 years, Francis was too busy to set aside twenty minutes to talk to Marie Collins or at least check to see if the only victim on the commission is OK. Or to see if it is too painful for her?", "id": "3ff3a01f-523d-4b10-a2e2-c33a8a866368", "ner": [["Francis", "PERSON"], ["Marie Collins", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I don't quite agree those were the issues, unless you mean to imply that white Catholics are more pro life anti gay marriage uber Catholics than Latino Catholics who went Clinton by a very large margin.", "id": "bd1fc3cb-a0c0-4070-9cbb-9bc1d784f2e7", "ner": [["Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Catholics", "NORP"], ["Catholics", "NORP"], ["Latino Catholics", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "I'll be on the look out tomorow a.m. so I can call the customer and let 'em know they can rock 'n roll on MTBE. Michael", "id": "bc51d906-f924-45eb-81a1-77241fa90179", "ner": [["Michael", "PERSON"], ["MTBE", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Lynch continues to take shots at DWR's LT contracts: FYI. See highlighted comments below. Don't know if you've heard, but there's considerable talk about Anthony trying to get the bonds out via Executive Order. How that might work technically is unclear", "id": "9b19e6a5-6120-414d-a032-d4c160834781", "ner": [["DWR", "ORG"], ["Executive Order", "ORG"], ["Lynch", "ORG"], ["Anthony", "PERSON"], ["Lynch", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Memo from Jeff Skilling: Dear Enron Employees: I am saddened to inform you that there was an explosion and fire at our Teesside power facility in England at approximately 2:40 p.m. local time. At this point, we know that two employees have died, and at least two others have been seriously injured. The area has been evacuated and the power station is currently off-line. The cause of the incident is not yet known. Our hearts and deepest sympathies go out to the families of those affected by this terrible incident. Jeff Skilling", "id": "d164e24a-706c-499a-b037-bea76f4af116", "ner": [["Jeff Skilling", "PERSON"], ["Jeff Skilling", "PERSON"], ["England", "GPE"], ["Teesside", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Mr. Seth was Governor Patricia's Commissioner of Administration. Do you really think he has any new ideas on the state budget?", "id": "fd4ec722-2b1b-4b5c-a802-a0d0e3d97acc", "ner": [["Patricia", "PERSON"], ["Seth", "PERSON"], ["Governor Patricia", "PERSON"], ["Mr. Seth", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"O getting smaller and smaller with each passing day.\" Christine Zavala That's a FACT! #MAGA #PMPK", "id": "9f1c1b7d-c591-49fd-92bc-1ebb3cf35545", "ner": [["MAGA", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["PMPK", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["MAGA", "ORG"], ["Christine Zavala", "PERSON"], ["PMPK", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Resumes - Thierry Noel & Tameeza Asaria: more from amanda m", "id": "882c8b8d-e7d3-4ef1-ac60-0aa86adaf92c", "ner": [["amanda m", "PERSON"], ["Thierry Noel", "PERSON"], ["Tameeza Asaria", "PERSON"], ["Resumes - Thierry Noel", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "_\"Trump because he is the only one who truly means what he says about bringing business back to America.\"_ This is sarcastic, eh? Otherwise, it can only be delusional. What jobs? Building a wall to keep out immigrants. -- Paul", "id": "ee9ad132-27cb-4c20-ad33-4c87da4cf7d4", "ner": [["America", "GPE"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Paul", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Was the work of Kristine Morgan cleared by the City Art Manager? Or is it only on the buses with routes outside of Alyssa?", "id": "0feed870-0379-497d-a374-b9a65bbae4d3", "ner": [["the City Art Manager", "ORG"], ["Kristine Morgan", "PERSON"], ["Alyssa", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "were given the option of seeking alternative electricity providers or buying power from Puget Sound Energy at rates capped at either $225 per megawatt hour or $100 less than the spot price on a major Northwestern U.S. spot-price market. Two even smaller users will simply buy their power at regulated rates. Puget Sound Energy also agreed not to recover any revenue lost because of the settlement from other residential and commercial ratepayers. Write to Donald Walker at robert.gavin@wsj.com", "id": "c0f8cdc7-79ba-4146-838d-3a507d8d7ffc", "ner": [["Donald Walker", "PERSON"], ["Puget Sound Energy", "ORG"], ["robert.gavin@wsj.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["robert.gavin@wsj.com", "USER_ID"], ["Puget Sound Energy", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Wrote in John Hunstman, Jr. He’s the former governor of Utah, who is very fiscally sound, but way too socially liberal for his home state. Served as Ambassador to China, and was just confirmed as Ambassador to Russia.", "id": "15891900-4adf-4d33-bc51-ac094ed02512", "ner": [["John Hunstman", "PERSON"], ["Russia", "GPE"], ["Utah", "GPE"], ["China", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "More importantly, pharmaceutical companies are now doing everything they can to increase drug prices, exponentially, it seems. The public was recently outraged when an ex-hedge fund manager bought the rights to the AIDS treatment drug, Daraprim, and raised the price from $13 to over $700 a dose.", "id": "1d580706-f51a-40de-b7f3-ecffbc635420", "ner": [["AIDS", "DISEASE"], ["Daraprim", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "And even when Hillary and her supporters spent twice as much as Trump to buy the Presidency, she still couldn't get there. It's so sad.", "id": "95c04eff-77c8-47fc-ac92-ca12c3bbbbe9", "ner": [["Hillary", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "\"A point that seems lost on you Jerome.\" Actually Clinton was charged with obstruction of justice, not having a fling with a willing adult. That seems to be a point lost on \"you\" liberals.", "id": "94734c9b-643c-47bd-b58e-3498b1f5b7d4", "ner": [["Jerome", "PERSON"], ["Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["liberals", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Clinton", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "By \"U of O Press Release\" do you mean the title of a post on the UO Matters Ethan? Those two things are wildly different. Also, it is 2016 and, even after three years have passed, UO is still in the AAU.", "id": "ec5299cb-6bd3-484d-a9f2-bc69c59298b3", "ner": [["U of O", "ORG"], ["AAU", "ORG"], ["Ethan", "PERSON"], ["UO", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Father Xavier wrote A JOURNAL of what happened at Vatican II. He wasn't INVENTING HISTORY. I have many histories of Vatican II----Rynne's account is concurred by the other histories as well.", "id": "5affcb81-2c8c-4c93-9c9f-7c467131db64", "ner": [["Rynne's", "PERSON"], ["Vatican II", "ORG"], ["Rynne", "PERSON"], ["JOURNAL", "ORG"], ["Vatican", "ORG"], ["Vatican", "ORG"], ["Xavier", "PERSON"], ["Vatican II", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "\"FBI uncovered 15,000 more documents in Clinton email probe\" - ADN. Sorry Ms. Clinton cannot be trusted.", "id": "2a2053ce-f9ff-4a07-9eb0-ad80e01a0ae5", "ner": [["Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["FBI", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "George lives in an air conditioned residence, works (if in fact he has a job) in an air conditioned space and rides in air conditioned vehicles. Isn't that right, George? George talks the talk. He DOES NOT walk the walk.", "id": "0e8a7335-f3ac-44e9-a51f-a314a683fecd", "ner": [["George", "PERSON"], ["George", "PERSON"], ["George", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "he wanted to talk about life after the sale of the pipeline, i.e. some people will be leaving the company (with the pipeline) , so he wants me to be ready to take on more responsibility -e Enron North America Corp. From: Ashley Garcia @ EES 01/26/2001 09:29 AM To: Tara HoffmanHOU/ECT@ECT cc:", "id": "34d78b46-df4a-4a7a-928f-6e84e6b42211", "ner": [["Tara Hoffman", "PERSON"], ["Enron", "ORG"], ["HOU/ECT@ECT", "USER_ID"], ["Ashley Garcia", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Matthew. The same to you - a very Happy Thanksgiving. Let's meet: I shall need more than one drink. Kara", "id": "d0cf2fa0-d06f-4b06-aa60-b0f3229f9ecd", "ner": [["Kara", "PERSON"], ["Matthew", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Julia, You Have New Southwest Classmates! (#77821201) : Hi, Julia. There's great news for you over at Classmates! You've asked us to keep track of your fellow Southwest classmates. The following are recent additions to your school:3 people found from the class of 1969 4 people found from the class of 1970 1 person found from the class of 1971 6 people found from the class of 1972 6 people found from the class of 1973 3 people found from the class of 1974 3 people found from the class of 1975 1 person found from the class of 1976", "id": "ef6a7067-43f3-41bd-8a96-cbfc83d9a4cc", "ner": [["Julia", "PERSON"], ["Julia", "PERSON"], ["#77821201", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "Legal Technology Team To All - We have a meeting scheduled for tomorrow at 2:30 in EB38C2. I am hoping to have a test version of the site available - especially since it is due for release on Friday. I have not been able to confirm its availability at this time. If it is not available, there is probably not a reason to meet tomorrow as I am sure we all have other projects. I will let you all know what the status is by late today or early a.m. tomorrow. Mark Senior Counsel, Anthony Jackson Facsimile:713-646-3940 E-Mail: Mark.Greenberg@enron.com", "id": "72e1de52-b3ce-4949-9c70-023f74df5d19", "ner": [["Mark.Greenberg@enron.com", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["713-646-3940", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Mark", "PERSON"], ["Senior Counsel", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Anthony Jackson", "PERSON"], ["reenberg@enron.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["EB38C2", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Legal Technology Team", "ORG"], ["Mark.Greenberg@enron.com", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "Catherine Huerta, Democrat from Texas is trying to. Democrat party leaders shut him down. Something about lack of evidence and can't just impeach based on emotions.", "id": "1e2f24ff-d866-4cc5-a2cc-36b9c2c728ea", "ner": [["Democrat", "NORP"], ["Catherine Huerta", "PERSON"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["Democrat", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "RIVERSIDE 6: As you may already know, Shari Stack will be handling this for ECT. SS", "id": "e27bae74-6339-4bc6-aedd-ad8aa7274c9f", "ner": [["SS", "ORG"], ["SS", "PERSON"], ["ECT", "ORG"], ["Shari Stack", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Same to you! And I hope you and your family have a HAPPY NEW YEAR! -E John Haley on 12/30/99 08:46:42 AM To: Nancy SchultzHOU/ECT@ECT cc:", "id": "a000639a-86ba-45ae-906a-14a5814a8921", "ner": [["E John Haley", "PERSON"], ["Nancy Schultz", "PERSON"], ["John Haley", "PERSON"], ["HOU/ECT@ECT", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "THEN get back to us with your revised lefty logic? ------- Most leftists do not sink so low in \"logic\" this is more like LOONY lefty people like Jane Doug Rachel Reyes and Tara Brown Cindy Mclaughlin", "id": "880d0159-3a87-4b9b-8275-1805f666a41c", "ner": [["Rachel Reyes", "PERSON"], ["Cindy Mclaughlin", "PERSON"], ["Tara Brown", "PERSON"], ["Doug", "PERSON"], ["Jane", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"To the contrary notwithstanding\" ....I'd know this was a Troy Perez essay if his name were left off ;) ! We're going to figure out how to get that written into his memorial someday. Perhaps channeling Dawn. Thanks for the great read, Professor!", "id": "ad5b56cf-8ef8-4226-84cb-a9240ae11b94", "ner": [["Troy Perez", "PERSON"], ["Dawn", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Workers at House Offices Begin Anthrax Treatment Senator Tom Daschle urged the nation to move quickly to expand its defenses against bioterrorism as workers in three congressional offices began protective treatment. http://www.nytimes.com/2001/10/28/politics/28ANTH.html? todaysheadlines", "id": "5706527b-c4b3-4abf-b62b-4f43c78233f7", "ner": [["congressional", "ORG"], ["Tom Daschle", "PERSON"], ["Anthrax", "DISEASE"], ["Offices", "ORG"], ["House", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "WR569 SPC report (750) : John, This is great! Would you send me copies for all the sites? Thanks, Linda", "id": "3c00288d-e6ac-4c91-8811-6e66b3790b68", "ner": [["WR569 SPC report (750)", "USER_ID"], ["Linda", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "You missed so much,, there are so many stores in businesses that need to be visited amongst them the painted pooch, Phoenix tea, Matthew Carter, the Oilerie, Burien press coffee shop,", "id": "25dfd354-5d58-46ff-8c90-7bc7150c293c", "ner": [["Oilerie, Burien press coffee shop", "ORG"], ["Phoenix tea", "ORG"], ["Matthew Carter", "PERSON"], ["Burien", "GPE"], ["the Oilerie", "GPE"], ["the Oilerie", "ORG"], ["Phoenix", "GPE"], ["Matthew Carter", "ORG"], ["Burien press", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Your note: my email as far as i know is jarnold@enron.com. not on msn though. i made space for your 8 people as well as ferries, roberts, and the other person (?? ) you requested. Come down tomorrow and i'll show you the layout again. john From: Frank Duncan/ENRON@enron Xgate on 04/30/2001 08:34 PM To: Dr. James ThomasECT@ECT cc:", "id": "2a09e6af-e52e-465b-9cea-d8e30c19b901", "ner": [["erries, roberts,", "PERSON"], ["f", "PERSON"], ["ferries", "PERSON"], ["ENRON", "ORG"], ["enron", "ORG"], ["Frank Duncan", "PERSON"], ["john ", "PERSON"], ["jarnold@enron.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["john", "PERSON"], ["@enron.com", "USER_ID"], ["msn", "ORG"], ["jarnold", "USER_ID"], ["roberts", "PERSON"], ["jarnold@enron.com", "USER_ID"], ["Dr. James Thomas", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Looking for any way to get away from the life and town he was born into, Tripp (Lucas Till), a high school senior, builds a ...", "id": "23a1795d-5bb3-489b-bf5a-6b56055f82a3", "ner": [["Lucas Till", "PERSON"], ["Tripp", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "$750 for being on standby and $750 for the power itself. Caps, if set too low, may dissuade companies from producing electricity and from building new power plants. ''If you fix caps at $250, you have to realize that if in a neighboring state someone is offering $251 for power, you will have a serious shortage,'' said Stephen Johnston, chairman of Duke Energy, a nationwide power generation and trading company. Given the complexities, deregulation, with its connotation of a laissez-faire management of an industry, seems a misnomer. The focus is now on reorganizing the electricity industry, rather than cutting it", "id": "80ba0aa9-ff94-4e05-959f-89bb66859815", "ner": [["Duke Energy", "ORG"], ["Stephen Johnston", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"Bills to \"build the wall\" could be marked up on Cinco de Mayo.\" \"Plans to cut military assistance to Europe could be rolled out on D-Day.\" What a refreshing piece. Contrast this with the typical droning of James Johnson and Kellie Shepherd...er, Christina.", "id": "136be715-b937-4b97-a017-afbda3deed66", "ner": [["James Johnson", "PERSON"], ["Kellie Shepherd", "PERSON"], ["Cinco de Mayo", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Christina", "PERSON"], ["Cinco de Mayo", "ORG"], ["Europe", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "I howled with laughter reading the first couple of paragraphs. Sean Avery doing Shakespeare. Enough said.", "id": "5f5f1341-400a-4bbb-97f7-7e75035be2a3", "ner": [["Shakespeare", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Shakespeare", "PERSON"], ["Sean Avery", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Jonan Gas Marketing Inc.: Laura, I have attached a simple release and settlement agreement for you use with the customer. Please call if you need anything further", "id": "e51e293a-933a-4e5c-b3c8-3fb5528ba10f", "ner": [["Jonan Gas Marketing Inc", "ORG"], ["Jonan Gas Marketing Inc.", "ORG"], ["Laura", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lal Echtenhoff: I just spoke with Kriste Sullivan about my response and she said it looks good. Let me know if you'd like to discuss, otherwise I'll send it out tomorrow. Thanks, Aaron", "id": "ece0435c-695b-4598-b564-900495b9c08c", "ner": [["Aaron", "PERSON"], ["Lal Echtenhoff", "PERSON"], ["Kriste Sullivan", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\"Many of the posts were left vacant for more than a year as an unfortunate consequence of Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell’s shameful decision to block President Barack Obama’s Supreme Court appointment.\" Are you still pretending it isn't?", "id": "eb06c49d-1bdc-4e36-8ee7-70fce4b5ced1", "ner": [["Mitch McConnell", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Supreme Court", "ORG"], ["Senate", "ORG"], ["Barack Obama", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "\"Now, the industry is down and out...\" Thanks for the chuckle. ExxonMobil's profits were $1.8 Billion for the first quarter of 2016. Ms. Andrea, please help me get to \"down and out.\"", "id": "c10447ee-134c-47bc-9bd6-0ae1c5378802", "ner": [["Andrea", "PERSON"], ["$1.8 Billion", "USER_ID"], ["ExxonMobil", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "So it's Lawrence and the Generals with Derrick doing background vocals", "id": "c23938b0-9f92-4b6a-81aa-5bf363c34314", "ner": [["Derrick", "PERSON"], ["Lawrence", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Tell me again, which is the party of deplorables? This ad is in keeping with the party whose vice president under Obama declared to a black audience that the Republicans would put them in chains. Who do these people think they are kidding.", "id": "c24962e9-9bf4-4545-a688-014fe37bcd30", "ner": [["Republicans", "NORP"], ["Obama", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
{"text": "Then she won two elections fair and square against Tony Knowles and Joe Miller. Alaskans know who is effective, experienced, and stands up for us. Lisa Murkowski!", "id": "421a35f5-62a6-49f1-8541-23fdba506cd6", "ner": [["Joe Miller", "PERSON"], ["Alaskans", "NORP"], ["Lisa Murkowski", "PERSON"], ["Tony Knowles", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "The polls are out of touch with reality, don't include anyone without a land line, almost zero people under 35, and no Independent voters. Clinton and Trump may be surprised by the back lash of mad voters, who will vote for someone more adult, Like Gary Johnson.", "id": "d0eef3a3-5e74-4346-bef7-1d10b8ad7a78", "ner": [["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Clinton", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Clinton", "PERSON"], ["Gary Johnson", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "The road will certainly make Bill Egan and Wally Hickel both smile from Heaven....it is now there and must be improved and its use expanded ...", "id": "6d0d7d45-67ec-4f09-b3cb-49ebc3955644", "ner": [["Bill Egan", "PERSON"], ["Wally Hickel", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "TW Tariff Language on OB As: Jennifer, If you have any problems, let me know. Otherwise, we'll talk later on how to resolve this. Mark http://www.tw.enron.com/twtariff/et_tf_curr_vol_frame.html Look at sheets 70 and 145-152 Elizabeth Benjamin 713-345-7896 office 713-822-4862 cell 713-646-2551 fax mark.mcconnell@enron.com", "id": "b4481f08-ff3a-4f54-b2d0-1579ef682745", "ner": [["Jennifer", "PERSON"], ["mark.mcconnell@enron.com", "USER_ID"], ["713-822-4862", "USER_ID"], ["mark.mcconnell@enron.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["TW", "ORG"], ["Elizabeth Benjamin", "PERSON"], ["713-646-2551", "USER_ID"], ["Mark", "PERSON"], ["http://www.tw.enron.com/twtariff/et_tf_curr_vol_frame.html", "USER_ID"], ["713-345-7896", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "VMUMC Website: I just wanted to inform you that the web site for Veterans has been updated and changed some. ? I ask that you would visit the site ?? ?? ? ?? ?? ?? www.veteransmemorialumc.homestead.com/veterans.html I encourage any suggestions or comments on how we may be able to improve the site. ? The second page is still under construction, so it is not completely finished. Deborah Nelson", "id": "bf02fcdf-6342-4d15-b2b5-80b087316930", "ner": [["VMUMC Website", "ORG"], ["VMUMC", "ORG"], ["www.veteransmemorialumc.homestead.com/veterans.html", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Deborah Nelson", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "USTIMENKO, OLGA PETROVNA was born 24 September 1983 and registered to vote in Broken Arrow, Oklahoma, U.S.A.", "id": "1f988ef7-da3e-41d5-8407-134c045b39b7", "ner": [["24 September 1983", "AGE"], ["Broken Arrow", "GPE"], ["USTIMENKO, OLGA PETROVNA", "PERSON"], ["U.S.A", "GPE"], ["OLGA PETROVNA", "PERSON"], ["U.S.A.", "GPE"], ["USTIMENKO", "ORG"], ["24 September 1983", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Oklahoma", "GPE"], ["USTIMENKO", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "But aren't you glad there are not innumerable diatribes about President Trump and Notre Dame???", "id": "734d042e-735d-40b8-8e98-a7fb75bb6556", "ner": [["Notre Dame", "ORG"], ["President Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Building apartments in Israeli cities and villages is not \"cruel, criminal course\". Bombing Israelis and villages with rockets, sending suicide bombers and killers - is exactly \"cruel, criminal course\". May be Palestinian Arabs should read Hosea 8:7. But likely they won't.", "id": "2d349ea9-15ab-4399-8603-3e020bef4c42", "ner": [["Hosea", "PERSON"], ["Palestinian Arabs", "NORP"], ["Israelis", "NORP"], ["Israeli", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Draft Meeting Notes From 11/8 SSG-WI Market Monitoring Working: My initial take is to keep engaged through Perrino. I'll try and make the call this Thursday. David", "id": "4d701da7-720c-48ae-a73a-92485b455448", "ner": [["SSG-WI Market", "ORG"], ["Perrino", "PERSON"], ["11/8 SSG-WI", "ORG"], ["David", "PERSON"], ["SSG-WI Market Monitoring", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Either Todd keeps his promise on repealing ACA, or he'll be replaced in 5 years. I suspect he's glad his reelection is 5 years away, and may be hoping people will forget his RINO vote in 2017.", "id": "190c857b-5d51-4a99-9f67-eacca8f4ad08", "ner": [["Todd", "PERSON"], ["RINO", "ORG"], ["ACA", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["ACA", "ORG"], ["RINO", "AMBIGUOUS"]]}
{"text": "??? Stephanie and her parlimentary secretary have been flying all over Europe the past few months and are still there now And Trudeau met with French PM on it today Very strange comment", "id": "dce7b42d-1b4f-45b0-a76b-7bd21998aeb9", "ner": [["Stephanie", "PERSON"], ["French", "NORP"], ["Trudeau", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Europe", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Meghan Williamson sales tax is deductible for Alaskans who pay no state income tax.", "id": "57976aa0-ba58-4504-808d-d7117f229b6e", "ner": [["Meghan Williamson", "PERSON"], ["Alaskans", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Meghan Boyd and Capacity Release Docs.: Please review and share your comments and concerns", "id": "1f6bc2a9-1f0c-4e86-9b87-ecec46bcdbea", "ner": [["Meghan Boyd", "PERSON"], ["Capacity Release", "ORG"], ["Capacity Release Docs", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "I'll agree with Mary Rebecca's Brennan's suggestion >35. Flower: anything tropical in fun bright colors (although you can hardly beat a fresh rose) >36. Least Favorite Food: bananas >37. Favorite Sports to Watch: Football (on TV and live)", "id": "f005f8fa-6ca0-4aa2-931c-049e21b18340", "ner": [["Mary Rebecca", "PERSON"], ["Brennan", "PERSON"], ["Least Favorite Food: bananas", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"], ["Mary Rebecca's", "PERSON"], ["Brennan's", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Favorite Sports to Watch: Football", "PERSONAL_ENTITY"]]}
{"text": "Loyal opposition....Patricia!!! If you, Allison and Thielen are the loyal opposition, does that make Gary a loyal supporter? As for refusing to remain silent, no one has heard from you guys all session, not even a peep out of your leader.", "id": "858f391f-efd3-447f-b7a7-773a9f8da54d", "ner": [["Thielen", "PERSON"], ["Allison", "PERSON"], ["Gary", "PERSON"], ["Patricia", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Since I moved back to Springfield and no longer have to pay Eugene taxes, the entire series of debacles that constitute Eugene City Government are much more entertaining than they used to be. Every now and then they reach the level of \"You can't make this stuff up!\"", "id": "6f0d28bb-5fdc-4cc1-9aa3-ec6db40f3759", "ner": [["Eugene City Government", "ORG"], ["Eugene", "GPE"], ["Eugene", "PERSON"], ["Springfield", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "So Cal Gas Files Motion with Bankruptcy Court Regarding Gas Business: FYI. I lifted this from So Cal Gas' responses filed today to PUC questions regarding our electric and gas activities in California. We may want to get our hands on the filing, which I do not have. Best, Jeff", "id": "4b03ab92-632c-40f0-a87e-7e79d4104cba", "ner": [["Jeff", "PERSON"], ["PUC", "ORG"], ["Bankruptcy Court", "ORG"], ["So Cal Gas", "ORG"], ["So Cal Gas", "ORG"], ["California", "GPE"]]}
{"text": "stocks hey, were you able to get MOT and Jennifer? Brett", "id": "aca7b08e-ef0f-4f15-9e92-ed908a06651d", "ner": [["Jennifer", "PERSON"], ["Brett", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "The Body Shop quick question Katherine, Just a quick question for you, please. I read the guidelines and included them below regarding the Body Shop. At the beginning of the page, it includes the category of employees to include some that I am not familiar with. Of course, I do see the area for contractors, however, I was curious what these classifications are. Can you please let me know what these are? New Power Company/Azurix/EDS Employees I just want to be sure on the correct fees prior to making a commitment to join with them. Also, have you ever been", "id": "b689c330-7607-4b38-935b-978a7ac08f8f", "ner": [["New Power Company/Azurix/EDS Employees", "ORG"], ["Azurix", "ORG"], ["EDS", "ORG"], ["the Body Shop", "ORG"], ["The Body Shop", "ORG"], ["Katherine", "PERSON"], ["New Power Company", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "TW Max Output & Add'l Capacity: How was this meeting? Any additional capacity identified? Thanks, Tyler", "id": "6a7672b0-31c6-4b19-ba6e-19b55ce018be", "ner": [["TW Max Output & Add'l Capacity", "ORG"], ["TW", "ORG"], ["Tyler", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "u aware of whalley meeting this pm re: settle SCE claims? jeff", "id": "664b8e11-a0a8-4a75-99bb-c1fab0df6099", "ner": [["whalley", "PERSON"], ["SCE", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["SCE", "ORG"], ["jeff", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Wheel SHAST Green Credits: Alyssa, I researched the Green Credits deals for 2000. I spoke with Kelly Ellison and he looked at the contracts. The prices for the months are as follows: August: $3 September: $3 October: $3 November: $1.50 December: $1.50 Here is my record of the what the Green Credit payments should be and I have confirmed that these match the spreadsheets on the Enron West site: August: $209.81 (no sheet on E'West for this month) September: $3177 October: $3444 November: $1773.45 (I updated the E'West spreadsheet, the price was already correct in our system) December: $1729.23 Thus,", "id": "99badd25-19eb-4fb5-94c0-19f28c1832cc", "ner": [["Enron", "ORG"], ["SHAST", "ORG"], ["Kelly Ellison", "PERSON"], ["Alyssa", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Zachariah and Elizabeth, also Mary and Joseph were married. Big difference from a creepy predator.", "id": "d6be9cf9-e227-4990-b479-87357a0f00a5", "ner": [["Elizabeth", "PERSON"], ["Joseph", "PERSON"], ["Zachariah", "PERSON"], ["Mary", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Groupdolists was born from the vision of founder Michael Sher, an entrepreneur with a track record of success in the emergency and incident management markets. Michael was most recently the co-founder of Send Word Now, which began in New York City following 9/11.", "id": "5247d829-9b65-4669-bc56-725ce12fdd3e", "ner": [["Michael", "PERSON"], ["Michael Sher", "PERSON"], ["New York City", "GPE"], ["Groupdolists", "NORP"]]}
{"text": "Robin read about how the Denver Broncos owner is releasing ownership of the team because he has Alzheimer's. Robin said that the sale of the team is up in the air right now.", "id": "2091072f-e22d-4c70-9906-53fa95538ef8", "ner": [["Robin", "PERSON"], ["Alzheimer's", "DISEASE"], ["Denver Broncos", "ORG"], ["Robin", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "At least Dungy and Harrison weren't among those commentators. http://www.denverbroncos.com/news-and-blogs/article-1/Dungy-Harrison-look-to-Trevor-Siemian-to-make-Broncos-passing-attack-more-explosive/75c490a8-b4b1-47e8-9b64-e2bb8001c83f Can't say the same for Bucky Brooks who said they would finish last in the AFC West and Dalllas would win.", "id": "129f46fb-573d-44d2-bb6a-172b9a0eb8bb", "ner": [["Dalllas", "PERSON"], ["Harrison", "PERSON"], ["Harrison", "PERSON"], ["http://www.denverbroncos.com/news-and-blogs/article-1/Dungy-Harrison-look-to-Trevor-Siemian-to-make-Broncos-passing-attack-more-explosive/75c490a8-b4b1-47e8-9b64-e2bb8001c83f", "USER_ID"], ["Dungy", "PERSON"], ["AFC", "ORG"], ["Bucky Brooks", "PERSON"], ["Dungy", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Daily Firm Contract: Thanks Michael. Do you have the form of discount letter too? If so, please send it. From: Michael Lee 03/10/2000 11:03 AM To: Rebecca Mason/ET&S/Enron@ENRON cc:", "id": "edeef2b2-da47-47b8-8181-466de265c209", "ner": [["Rebecca Mason", "PERSON"], ["Michael", "PERSON"], ["Michael", "PERSON"], ["ET&S/Enron@ENRON", "USER_ID"], ["Michael Lee", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "DP Question: Jeff: You asked how your Gross Margin % could be higher in 2000 but your overall Gross Margin be lower. You appear to have lower invoiced volumes in Jan-April 2000. January and Feb. -for example: Great question! Dave", "id": "9a9d695c-3c15-4a66-b83e-af3ad47ec748", "ner": [["Dave", "PERSON"], ["Gross Margin %", "PERSON"], ["Jeff", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "EJ Office Opening Mike, Certainly appreciate you visiting the office and helping with the opening... not the least shaking over 300 hands and breaking the barrell. Sorry we were not able to spend some time discussing business. We did get some good time with Allison on Wednesday. I understand we will now be on a weekly call. Natalie seemed to be satisfied with the opening. His visit has done quite a lot for us. thanks, Sharon", "id": "b0372649-834f-46c7-b2ab-f0a467c8817d", "ner": [["EJ", "PERSON"], ["Allison", "PERSON"], ["Natalie", "PERSON"], ["EJ Office Opening Mike", "ORG"], ["Sharon", "PERSON"], ["Mike", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "ENA - West Gas Pricing Sheet: Mark, I was looking at that pricing sheet and would like to suggest that the shading in the commentary boxes... under the assumption that this becomes a printed document and that it is printed in black & white, it is very difficult to read. Perhaps a more solid background would work better. Timothy", "id": "3abcf347-ce46-4d8e-93bc-3bbb7dedf55f", "ner": [["ENA - West Gas Pricing Sheet", "ORG"], ["Timothy", "PERSON"], ["ENA", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Haha. Same with people flapping their cyberjaws about how horrible the Dolphins did under Alison last year. News bulletin: He's not the DC here. The DC is doing just fine.", "id": "17c52a41-bc76-44b4-91c2-d5377680989b", "ner": [["DC", "GPE"], ["DC", "GPE"], ["Alison", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Has the FEC investigated Bonnie Ray giving the debate questions to Hillary yet??? She's admitted it. Should be an easy collar.", "id": "279120b2-8729-4dd6-ad33-e1c349492f67", "ner": [["Bonnie Ray", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["FEC", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Here's how dealings with Russian bank under sanctions worked: http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2017/08/trumps-moscow-partner-was-apparently-financed-by-a-russian-bank-under-us-sanctions/ Think if all that was going on, Jr., William, and maybe even Whitney didn't know about it, and try to get in on the action?", "id": "be5205df-08f8-46fb-9228-c4d74753be97", "ner": [["Russian", "NORP"], ["Whitney", "PERSON"], ["William", "PERSON"], ["moscow", "GPE"], ["http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2017/08/trumps-moscow-partner-was-apparently-financed-by-a-russian-bank-under-us-sanctions/", "USER_ID"]]}
{"text": "Hey Jorge: I tried to add you to my MSN Instant Messenger service but Enron's email firewall has heightened it's security disabling me to log into outside email accounts. Later after everything cools off and they ease up on the security we can use the instant messenger service. That church was a little slow compared to what I'm used too. It might be due to the fact that they are an interracial congregation. What is your friends name again that goes there", "id": "5bd6b8d8-3655-42b5-a2b5-8b1f810748fc", "ner": [["Jorge", "PERSON"], ["MSN", "ORG"], ["Enron", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "I came in late because of my back - I think I am going to go to a chiropractor \" Gregory Warner \" on 04/02/2001 08:04:09 AM To: kim.ward@enron.com cc:", "id": "1da2c66b-c369-443a-8d97-216d3508696b", "ner": [["04/02/2001", "GPE"], ["kim.ward@enron.com", "USER_ID"], ["kim.ward@enron.com", "IGNORE_ME"], ["04/02/2001", "AMBIGUOUS"], ["Gregory Warner", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Let’s contrast this story with Gail Collins anti-Trump Veterans’ column in today’s Register Guard and see which one we prefer. She certainly demonstrates media bias against him rather than an actual analysis of what happened to the $5 Million plus.", "id": "486b6195-e733-4806-b6c0-00e522ce795c", "ner": [["Veterans", "NORP"], ["Gail Collins", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"], ["Register Guard", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Meter 1517: I have created deal 244531 to cover this flow. Deborah Ortiz This is actually volume related to the term deal 93804. Volume flowed in March due to timing on changing the meter. Can you attach the term contract to this deal? (I copied the term deal to create the March ticket.) D Wendy Young 04/14/2000 09:01 AM To: Samuel BeasleyECT@ECT cc: Leah SmithCorp/Enron@ENRON", "id": "60f8f39e-f1f1-430d-8952-aab67c2b8eda", "ner": [["Samuel Beasley", "PERSON"], ["93804", "USER_ID"], ["Deborah Ortiz", "PERSON"], ["Wendy Young", "PERSON"], ["244531", "USER_ID"], ["ECT@ECT", "USER_ID"], ["ENRON", "ORG"], ["Meter 1517", "USER_ID"], ["Enron", "ORG"], ["Leah Smith", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Oh dear us.. Like Michael Gonzalez and company don't worship the Aryan master race.", "id": "3936ab99-0065-46dd-9304-dde166f0662a", "ner": [["Aryan", "NORP"], ["Michael Gonzalez", "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Poor RD, once again, he shows that he is unable to comprehend the English language. He complains that Pope Michael is saying something that, in fact, he did not say. I wonder which diploma mill he got his \"PhD\" from, since his reading skills are so poor.", "id": "7c77a1b6-2bcb-4a0d-8359-410551fa0d86", "ner": [["Michael", "PERSON"], ["RD", "ORG"]]}
{"text": "The late Brian Weber. However if you're comparing Trump's wit to a machine gun, you are sadly mistaken.", "id": "005c2d69-f9cb-403c-9a97-d834dbd04e3f", "ner": [["Brian Weber", "PERSON"], ["Brian", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PUBLIC_FIGURE"]]}
